Guide to the Hardy Jenkinson family home movies 1959-1961
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
Hardy Jenkinson family home movies
1951-1969
University of Utah Libraries, Special Collections Audio Visual Archives Special Collections 295 South 1500 East Salt Lake City, Utah 84112-0860 (801) 581-8864
A0827
Jenkinson, Hardy
19 8mm films
The Hardy Jenkinson family home movies (1951-1969) consist of family and vacation footage including footage of river-running throughout Utah and the surrounding areas.
The Hardy Jenkinson family home movies (1951-1969) consist of family and vacation footage including footage of river-running throughout Utah and the surrounding areas.
The materials are arranged chronologically.
Materials must be used on-site; no use of original material, access copies will be made available for viewing. Five business days advanced notice required. Access to parts of this collection may be restricted under provisions of state or federal law, condition of the material, or by donor.
Utah; Colorado River (Colo.-Mexico); Rivers--Recreational use; Sports and Recreation; Moving Images; Moving images
- Colorado River trip, 1951 May; 8mm film (Reel 1)
- Uncle Joe's; Terri's 4th birthday, 1951-1956; 8mm film (Reel 2)
- Bryce Canyon; Bear Lake; Winder Dairy; Christmas, 1957; 8mm film (Reel 3)
- Winter; Mirror Lake; Madison River; Topaz Mountain; 4th of July; Terri's 5th birthday; Circle Cliffs, 1957-1958; 8mm film (Reel 4)
- California; Bill and Nita's; Christmas; Terri's 6th birthday; Summer, 1959; 8mm film (Reel 5)
- Bill and Nita Goodes; Topaz Mountain; 4th of July; Manila; Cristmas 1959; Terri's 7th birthday; Browne Lake; Flaming Gorge, 1959-1960; 8mm film (Reel 6)
- Summer; Disneyland; Racetrack; Marineland of Pacific part one, 1961; 8mm film (Reel 7)
- Marineland of Pacific part two; Verbal; deer and pheasant hunt, 1961; 8mm film (Reel 8)
- Pack trip; Red Castle Lake, 1962; 8mm film (Reel 9)
- Pack trip; Pine Island Lake, 1961; 8mm film (Reel 10)
- 1961 Christmas; 1962 Freights to Alaska; 1962 Christmas; 1963 zacation at Moon Lake, 1961-1963; 8mm film (Reel 11)
- 1963 elk hunt; 1963 Halloween; 1963 Christmas; 1964 Spring; 1964 Christmas; Winter, 1963-1964; 8mm film (Reel 12)
- 1965 pack trip to East Basin; 1967 Natural Bridges, etc., 8mm film (Reel 13)
- Untitled film, 1965; 8mm film (Reel 14)
- Vacation, 1968; 8mm film (Reel 15)
- Untitled film, circa 1968-1969; 8mm film (Reel 16)
- Jenkinson family reunion, 1969; 8mm film (Reel 17)
- Fun - 1st film, undated; 8mm film (Reel 18)
- Untitled film, undated; 8mm film (Reel 19)